girlsgames24.com 2018-09-02

# Privacy Policy - Girls Games 24

On this page we will explain our terms and conditions applying to your online privacy. Girlsgames24.com cares about your privacy and will do efforts to make your visits to our girl games portal private and enclosed. However there are a few issues that you need to be aware of while visiting our free game service for girls: 

**Full Privacy**

girlsgames24.com is committed to protecting your privacy online. girlsgames24.com does not collect any personal information.

Girlgames24.com is safe place to play free games for girls.

**No IP address and logging**

Your IP address is not used to gather broad demographic information and we do not track your general visiting paterns (how many pages you view while at one website, downloads, etc). There is no system on our server to store / process information about our traffic or users. Normal log files are disabled on our server, the current log level is set on EMERG, meaning the server will only create an emergency log file in the event of a server crash. We are here to create a safe and free girl game experience!

**Sharing Of Information**

There are no scripts or programs running on our server that store your information. We allow our third party advertisers to host scripts on our webpages. Third party advertisers might collect, store and use your information. These scripts are not property of our game portal website and are subject to the privacy policy of the third party. Find the links to the third party privacy policies in the sections below to learn more.

**Third Party Advertising**

We use third-party advertising companies to serve ads when you visit girlsgames24.com. These companies may use information (not including your name, address, email address or telephone number) about your visits to this and other Web sites in order to provide advertisements on this site and other sites about goods and services that may be of interest to you. Please visit cpmstar.com and google.com/adsense to learn more about the third party policies and their current privacy statements.

**Third Party Cookies**

In the course of serving advertisements to this site, our third-party advertiser may place or recognize a unique cookie on your browser. The sripts of our third parties are not located on our server.

Google Adsense : [www.google.com/adsense](https://www.google.com/adsense)  
Google Cookies Policy : [google.com/privacy_cookies.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_cookies.html)  
Adsense Privacy policy : [google.com/privacy_ads.html](http://www.google.com/privacy_ads.html)  
Cpmstar Privacy Policy : [www.cpmstar.com](http://www.cpmstar.com/)

**What Are Cookies?**

Cookies are digital text files that can be created by any remote connection that you make in your browser. A cookie can only store text or (binairy) numbers or a combinations of both. Because cookies are just text files, created and controlled by your browser, it's a harmless system for your computer health. However you need to be aware that websites, mobile apps and advertisers are able to write and read certain 'invisible' information on the background while you think you are just browsing some online or mobile App content. Our website is NOT using performance cookies and is NOT tracking your behaviour. However we are using third-party advertisers that might use cookies - please read the third party section of our privacy policy for more information about our third parties.

**Opt Out**

You could opt-out cookies from third parties by using services provided by networkadvertising.org. Please click [here](http://www.networkadvertising.org/managing/opt_out.asp) to learn more about this option. **Note:** this service will actually create cookies itself too, please read their TOS fully to understand the risks.

**Liability**

It is girlsgames24.com's policy to respond quickly to claims of intellectual property violation. Upon receiving notification in accordance with any related copyright organization or owner, girlsgames24.com will immediately disable and remove games in question.
